https://masksoftheworld.com/privacy-policy/

Misc
Is Your Mask Rare and Valuable?
Misc
Is Your Mask Rare and Valuable?
Masks of the World – Book
Masks of World – Book
Learn more about our Mask of the World Book
Information We Collect
Masks of the World collects information about the use of the service to provide a secure and personalized experience. This includes the customer’s name, purchasing records, and shopping patterns.
We may collect information when you: (a) place an order; (b) send email messages or other information to us.
Disclosure of Information
We do not sell, rent, or loan your information to third parties without your permission. So, for example, we do not sell your email address or other information to mass marketers. Masks of the World affiliates will be allowed to contact you with special offers and information related to products you have bought, shopped for or expressed interest in.
Privacy Protection for Children
In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we do not knowingly provide our service to persons under the age of 13.
Log Files
Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Content
For purposes of this policy “content” means a creative expression and includes, without limitation, video, audio, photographs, images, illustrations, animations, logos, tools, written posts, replies, comments, information, data, text, software, scripts, executable files, graphics, and interactive features, any of which may be generated, provided, or otherwise made accessible on masksoftheworld.com or our partner sites.
When you provide content to masksoftheworld.com, you grant masksoftheworld.com a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free, sublicensable, transferable right and license to use, host, store, cache, reproduce, publish, display (publicly or otherwise), perform (publicly or otherwise), distribute, transmit, modify, adapt (including, without limitation, in order to conform it to the requirements of any networks, devices, services, or media through which the Services are available), and create derivative works of, such content.
Web Cookies and Beacons
Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user.
Web beacons are objects that are embedded in a webpage or email that are invisible to the user, but allow checking that a user has viewed the page or email. Other names are web bug, tracking bug, tag or page tag.
This website does use cookies. Additionally, some of my business partners may use cookies and web beacons as well. This site has no control of advertisers’ web cookies or web beacons.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. Please check your browser’s help section for instructions on how to do this.
Links
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy policy (or privacy statement) of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.
Advertisers
We may use outside advertising networks and companies in order to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons in order to collect data in the ad serving process. These cookies and/or web beacons are collected by the companies and/or advertising networks.
Contact Information
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the Masks of the World privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Reject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
